<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MCPserved</string>

    <string name="a11y_label">MCPserved</string>
    <string name="a11y_description">Lets a desktop client you have paired read the screen and dispatch touches on your behalf, restricted to the applications you explicitly grant. The client connects only over a local loopback port you bridge yourself with adb; nothing is reachable from the network, nothing is reachable until you grant it, and every action is logged in an ongoing notification while a session is open.</string>
    <string name="notif_listener_label">MCPserved notifications</string>

    <string name="channel_session">Session</string>
    <string name="channel_session_desc">Shows while MCPserved is armed or a session is open.</string>

    <string name="notif_armed">MCPserved armed</string>
    <string name="notif_armed_body">Listening. No session open.</string>
    <string name="notif_active">Session active · %1$ds left</string>
    <string name="notif_active_body">Backends: %1$s</string>

    <string name="action_stop">Stop session</string>
    <string name="action_revoke_all">Revoke all</string>
    <string name="action_disarm">Disarm</string>

    <string name="disclosure_title">Before you begin</string>
    <string name="disclosure_intro">MCPserved lets a desktop client you pair with this device read the screen and perform taps, swipes, and text entry on your behalf, so that an assistant running on your own computer can operate the phone for you.</string>
    <string name="disclosure_a11y_title">It uses the Accessibility Service</string>
    <string name="disclosure_a11y_body">To read the screen and dispatch input it relies on Android\'s Accessibility Service. That is a powerful permission. This app uses it only to carry out the actions the paired client requests, and only for the applications you explicitly grant.</string>
    <string name="disclosure_local_title">It stays on your device</string>
    <string name="disclosure_local_body">The client connects over a local connection you set up yourself with adb (USB, or adb-over-Wi-Fi). The app makes no connection to the internet and sends your screen contents to no server. Nothing is reachable from the network.</string>
    <string name="disclosure_control_title">You stay in control</string>
    <string name="disclosure_control_body">Nothing can happen until you enable the service, pair a client, arm the app, and grant specific packages. Each session is time-limited and shown in an ongoing notification you can stop from at any moment, and every action is logged while a session is open. An empty grant list leaves the app unable to touch anything.</string>
    <string name="disclosure_agree">By continuing, you agree to let MCPserved use the Accessibility Service for this purpose.</string>
    <string name="disclosure_accept">I understand and agree</string>
    <string name="disclosure_decline">Not now</string>
</resources>
